<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on Tiger Soup</title>
    <link>http://sumitii.github.io/tigersoup/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on Tiger Soup</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 11:35:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://sumitii.github.io/tigersoup/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Challenges</title>
      <link>http://sumitii.github.io/tigersoup/about/challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 11:35:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sumitii.github.io/tigersoup/about/challenges/</guid>
      <description>Overcapacity + Compressed Demand   Growth will require keeping your own customers while stealing those from competitors. Requirements: Renewed focus on keeping every single customer; improving customer experiences; getting more strategic and competitive marketing campaigns; improve customer service.
 Counteracting competitive aggression   Expect leading competitors to upgrade their advertising campaigns in all media. Requirements: Build stronger intelligence on competitors; improve speed to market; talk to your own customers and invest in differentiating your brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we do</title>
      <link>http://sumitii.github.io/tigersoup/about/wwd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 11:35:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sumitii.github.io/tigersoup/about/wwd/</guid>
      <description>The new reality facing companies is that markets have shrunk and winning now requires taking a new kind of fight to the marketplace. Like catching a tiger, this can be a tough undertaking. One that takes special skills and deep understanding of the dynamics of industry segments. Stealing customers from competitors as they grow ever-more aggressive in attempting to do the same thing to you will be the name of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>